Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audio visual materials, 1965-2005; Series 8
  - CGA Interview David Levy, President, 1996 February 9; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - CGA Interview David Levy, President, 1996 February 9; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - "Scholastic Art Writing Awards 1993", Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Elissa Black Free (Unknown), 1997 January 28; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Jill Rappaport: Today Show, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Sponsored by Rockefeller Foundation, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - American Russian Cultural Cooperation Foundation CGA, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Russia Today Promo, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - [Unknown], Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - A New Vision in Communications AT, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - GMA Sunda Postman, 1997 February 2; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Gordon Parks at CGA, 1996 March 29; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Gordon Parks at CGA, 1996 March 29; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Hot Tickets Segment, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Gordon Parks at CGA, 1996 March 29; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Horizons TV, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Black History Month Making History Now, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Better Late Than Never, 1994 June 26; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Teen TV Feature on the Corcoran Art Mentorship Program, 1997 April 5; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Making History New, 1997 February 12; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Copy of Media Coverage of Fannie Mae Event, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - [Unknown], Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Around Town, Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - [Russia Today TV Journal], Circa 1989-1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Bosnia Art Exhibit WTTG-TV5 10PM News, 1994 April 16; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Professor Bill Newman WJLA-TV7 5PM News, 1994 June 13; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Sunday Morning News Blacks in Art, 1990 February 4; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - CBS News Nightwatch Guy Mcelroy, 1990 January 24; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Around Town #611, 1990 December 13-15; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Fox/WTTG 10PM News "Single in the City" featuring the Corcoran's 1869 Society, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - The Art's Build Communities VACOP Ceremony, 1994 November 22; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Visions Del Pueblo PSA's English/Spanish Version, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports 1989, Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Computer Instructions Backup Sections, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Navy Band CDR. Ned Muffley Conducting, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Film Reel, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Film Reel, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Amon Carter Museum, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Corcoran School of Art, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Art Exhibits, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Press Info. + Annual Report, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Micro Ten Pak, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Message, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Renee Montagne.Corcoran Morning Edition, 1989 June 16; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Motley Jazz, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - National Public Radio Morning Edition Side 12, 1994 January 18; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Works on Paper, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - New York 60-Year Retrospective CGA WTOP Radio, Washington, DC, 1988 February 13-14; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - National Public Radio Morning Edition Side 34, 1994 January 18; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Cartridge Printwheel II, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Diane Rohm DAR, 1995 October 5; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Robert Mapplethorpe Exhibit Sandy Payton Show, 1989 June 21; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - At The Corcoran Terry Saltan "James Drake", Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - "Corcoran Gallery" 2 Segments/Schedule on Cover, 1995 November 16-17; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - "Robert Mapplethorpe Exhibit" News WBUR-FM/Boston, 1989 June 16; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - WTOP-AM News, 1995 March 21; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - WDCY - FM 90.1 Mundo Latino, 1987 October 20; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - At the Corcoran w/ Anne Balir Dennis Reed, 1989 August 27; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - "Roy Lichtenstein: Past Present + Future" CGA, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Temple of Confessions Documentary No Dolby, 1996; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - At the Corcoran w/ Anne Blair, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - At the Corcoran / Anne Blair All Things Considered, 1986 July 28; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 38)
  - Mr. David Levy, Director CGA, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Corcoran 9-11 Scott, 1992 June 11; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 40)
  - The Diane Rehm Show Danny Lyon Pt. 12, 1994 February 7; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - "Robert Mapplethorpe Exhibit" News WHUR-FM/Washington, DC, 1989 June 16; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Outgoing Message, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 43)
  - Lenette Johnson, WDCU (education) panelist discussing "Art Jazz", 1992 November 24; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 44)
  - Diane Rehm Show Open Phones, 1989 June 14; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 45)
  - Floppy Disks, Circa 1989-1999; Series 8 (Box 84, Folder 46)
  - Eyewitness News "Gallery" Topkapi, 2000 March; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - National Arts (Danny Buraczeski and Milt Hinton), Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - ESSO Presents "New Worlds from Old", 1999 January; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - "Jack Cowart/Corcoran Gallery", 1997 August 28; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs Sunday Morning Harlem Renaissance, 1998 August; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Rockwell Newshour, 2000 July 4; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - American-Russian Cultural Cooperation Foundation CGA Jewels of the Romanovs, 1997 February 10; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Faberge Exhibit at Corcoran Gallery, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Sunday Morning Harlem Renaissance, 1998 August 9; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Ken Aptekar Talking to Pictures, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art: Jewels of the Romanovs, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Nancy Chunn Dub from VHS Global Views CNN, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Sunday Morning Arnold Newman, 2000 March 19; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Around Town, 1998 February 5; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Jack Cowart, 1997 Re: Stolen Rembrandts, Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - America, America Program #39, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - African Women in the Arts, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Ruby Bridges/Rockwell Today Show-NBC, 2000 August 10; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Biennial Symposium 98, 1998; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Ultimate 10 Amazing Treasures Jewels of the Romanovs, 2000 December; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - America, America Program #38, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Think Tank - Rockwell, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Chihuly Over Venice, 1996 February; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - CGA Jewels of the Romanovs B Roll, Circa 1996-2000; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Rockwell: The Measure of the Man, 2000 September 14; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Earthquack Italy Guest Susan Badder, 1997 September 26; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Rockwell What Makes Him Good, 2000 July 26; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - NBC - VACOP, 1997; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Around Town, 1998; Series 8 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Lou Stovall - Printmaker, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Sidney Lawrence Criticism, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Alfredo, Kentse Susan Bader Victoria, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Freshmen 1989 Rouday Truce Performance Class, Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Fall '97 Strategies of Criticism Dec 9 Mark Power, 1997 December 9; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Ceridwen Morris Critiques Seminar, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Corcoran School of Art Commencement 1990 Dennis Barry, Commencement Speaker Producer/Director of Tape C. Graham, Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Fall '97 Strategies of Criticism Sept. 30 Andrew Hudson, 1997 September 30; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Nov. 12th Claudine Alex Susan Bader, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Sarah Hyde: Luke, Joe, Jesse, Patrick, 1998 November 17; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Jack Cowart, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Doug Lang Fall 98, 1998; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran Gallery VHS #1 Includes Tapes 1,2,3, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Corcoran/IAF - (Lima-Peru) Photography Month - Sept. 99, 1999 September; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Andrew Hudson Critique Session, 1996; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - For the Love of Paint: Recents Works By Franklin White, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Fall '97 Strategies of Criticism September 23 Bernard Welt, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Rex!, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Fall '97 Strategies of Criticism Nov. 4 Jack Cowart, November 4; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Crits with Andrea Pollan, 1996 November 24; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Fall '97 Stragtegies of Criticism Nov. 18, 1997 November 18; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Sidney Lawrence: Criticism Week 3 Tape 1, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Terry Sultan Critique Sessions, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Fall 1998 Criticism Seminar Sept. 22 Bernard Welt., Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Leggz, 2003 May 30; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - Criticism Seminar Week 4 Phillip Brookman, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - Video Workshop Freshmen 1990 Christiane Graham/Lynn Sures CSA, Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Fall '97 Strategies of Criticism Oct. 14 Ferdinand Protzman, 1997 Octoober 14; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - Fall '97 Strategies of Criticism Oct. 7 Doug Lang, Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - Midnight Movers, 2003 June 20; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - [10 Packets of Photos from Ritz Big Print Central], Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - [5 Packets of Photos from Penn Camera], Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - 2 Loose Papers, Circa 1990-1999; Series 8 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Photography: Where We Are Tape 1 Sontag/Kramer, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - 23rd Area Exhibition: Video The Corcoran Gallery of Art Washington, D.C., Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - 23rd Area Exhibition: Video The Corcoran Gallery of Art Washington, D.C. Master A, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - 23rd Area Exhibition: Video The Corcoran Gallery of Art Washington, D.C. Master B, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - 23rd Area Exhibition: Video The Corcoran Gallery of Art Washington, D.C. Dub from Master A, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Photography: Where We Are Tape 2 Bunnell/Wagstaff, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - James A. Michener Art Museum Video Exhibits Edward W. Redfield, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - CGA Weddings, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Copy of WJZ TV Story 50 Ships in My Front Yard, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - In Response to Place Executive Version, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - 23rd Area Exhibition: Video Beta Tape, Circa 1978-2005; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Frank Gehry Lecture Corcoran Gallery, 1997 November; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Winslow Homer CGA, 1991 May 9; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Tape of Jenna Marshall's (VOA) Interview with Walter Hopps, 1971 April 15; Series 8 (Box 130, Folder 14)
- Design records, 2004-2008; Series 9
  This series contains records that detail the work of the Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics division of the Corcoran Gallery of Art and the Corcoran College of Art + Design. These records date primarily from 2004-2008.
  - Modernism Shop, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - 1031-01 Modernism Ads, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - 1031-38 Shop Stanchion Sign, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - 1031-23 Museum Store, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - 1031-20 Map, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Modernism-Stanchions, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Modernism Pitch Package, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Modernism Contractual, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Sympossium 1031-33, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Spring Into Modernism, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Modernism Objects, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Modernism-Adman, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Modernism - Identity, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Modernism - Loose, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - 1031-16 Modernism Press Package, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - 1031-26 Press Preview Day, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Modernism-Student Timeline, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Modernism Floor Plans, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - 1031-30 Exploration Gallery Booklet, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Modernism-Visitor Guide Book, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - Loose Modernism, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - Modernism Banners, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - 1031-18 Exterior Banner, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - Modernism Store Collateral, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - 1031-23 Shop Stanchion, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - 1031-03 MOD Signboards 2, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - 1031-25 Motel Collateral Hotel Desk Signage, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - 1031-06 Please Do Not Touch, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 28)
  - 1031 - Education Gallery Retracteable Banner, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  - Ticket Master Front and Back, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 30)
  - Ticketmaster, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 31)
  - 1031 Ticket Insert, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  - 1031-03/18 Signboard + Banners, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 33)
  - 1031 Crash Course Card, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 34)
  - 1031-13 Modernism Soft Cover, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 35)
  - 1031-22 Modernsim Postcards, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 36)
  - 1031-25 Rack Cards, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 37)
  - Modernism - Vouchers, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 38)
  - 1031-01 Advertising Modernism, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 39)
  - 1031-37 Table Text, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 40)
  - Opening Invitations, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 41)
  - 1024-05 Modernism Menu, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 42)
  - Modernism - Colour, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 43)
  - Modernism - Colour Continued, Circa 2006-2007; Series 9 (Box 137, Folder 44)
  - 1068-08 Works on Paper Object Labels, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - 1018-11 Expressions / Wall Txt, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - 1018-11 Expressions, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - 1094-01 Alumni Events Invite, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - 1043-12 Camp Creativity Banners, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Womens Committee - Save The Date, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Temporary Membership Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Tim Gunn Invite, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Missing Items '06, 2006; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - 1013.01_Special Events Collateral, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Correspondance Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Off The Walls, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Elsa - Off the Wall, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - CE; Off+W Mem, AD, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - BOT Folder Inserts, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Marriot, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - MA Open House PC 06, 2006; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Jeanne Weaver Ruesch, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - CE + Open Housecard Nov. 06, 2006 November; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - PDay 06 - Brochure, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - 1024_JOA Family Day 0/07 Stanchions, 2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - 1024_02 Comment Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - 1024_02 US Comment Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - 10 Salon Dore Brochure, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - 1040-06 Preview Day Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Art Centric, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Art Centric '06, 2006; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - 1061-01 Gallery 31 Post Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - Security - Cards, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - 1040-07 Dean's Invitation, 2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Member Event Template, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - 1007-12 member Buckslip, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Ted Turner Invite, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - Student Membership Card - Pending, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - 1007-14 Member Bookmark, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Member Shopping Day, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - I-Mem Preview Day Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 37)
  - I-Mem BMW Imprint, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 38)
  - I-Mem Friends Imprint, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 39)
  - I-Mem Members Shopping Day Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 40)
  - I-Mem 1809 Imprint, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 41)
  - I-Mem Corcoran Member Calendar Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 42)
  - I-Mem Student Membership Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 43)
  - I-Mem Joan of Arc Invite, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 44)
  - I-Mem Charman's Guild Invite, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 45)
  - 1024 06 Coffee BOT, 2006; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 46)
  - 1007-16 Art Forum, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 47)
  - Art Forum - 06, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 48)
  - Closed for the Day 1091-001 Glass Stanchion Signs, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 49)
  - Cafe Menu, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 50)
  - Holiday Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 51)
  - IA- Halloween Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 52)
  - ME-Halloween Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 53)
  - Holiday Card '06, 2006; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 54)
  - ME-Family Day P Card, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 55)
  - I--Mem 1889 Fall Fete, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 56)
  - Corporate Membership, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 57)
  - Signboards / PI JOA, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 58)
  - Gonzalez, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 59)
  - Bechtle: Retrospecttive, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 60)
  - Bob Bechtle updates, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 61)
  - 1034-09 Postcard Book, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 62)
  - 1009-05 1869 Invite, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 63)
  - 1017-02 Dudley Brochure, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 64)
  - 52nd Corcoran Ball, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 65)
  - Exhibitions at the Corcoran, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 66)
  - Other Projects for Washington Flyer, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 67)
  - Weingarten Ads, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 68)
  - Capitol File Ad - 1206, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 69)
  - Wash. Post Ad 11/06, 2006 November; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 70)
  - Ads - JOA, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 71)
  - 1003-20 On View Poster, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 72)
  - Banjo Show, Circa 2005-2007; Series 9 (Box 139, Folder 73)
  - Black Tie Invite 2006, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - 1869, 2005, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - 1869, 2006, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Otto Reusch invite, Circa 2004-2006; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - SIS postcard 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Membership postcard 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Special Events Invite 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Fall 2005 Style, Circa 2004-2006; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Member Holiday Shopping 2005, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Magnets 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - 2006 Membership Brochure, Circa 2004-2006; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Membership Preview Day Postcard 2005, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Membership, Circa 2004-2006; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - BPW invite 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Travels 2005, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Wash Post Ad 2005, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - WHNPA 2006,2004, 2004-2006; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Reception Invites 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Open House Invite 2004, Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - WPA/C, Circa 2004-2006; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Night, 2004 January; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Night, 2004 February; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Night, 2004 March; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - Night, 2004 April; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Night, 2004 May; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 25)
  - Night, 2004 June; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 26)
  - Night, 2004 July; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 27)
  - Night, 2004 September; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 28)
  - Night, 2004 October; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 29)
  - Night, 2004 December; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 30)
  - Night, 2005 February; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 31)
  - Night, 2005 April; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 32)
  - Night, 2005 March; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 33)
  - Night, 2005 May; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 34)
  - Night, 2005 June; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 35)
  - Night, 2005 July; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 36)
  - Night, 2005 September; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 37)
  - Night, 2005 October; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 38)
  - Night, 2005 November; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 39)
  - Night, 2005 December; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 40)
  - Night, 2006 January; Series 9 (Box 140, Folder 41)